[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 13, "question": "Could Newt Gingrich be the next best hope for the GOP?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "Newt", "Gingrich", "be", "the", "next", "best", "hope", "for", "the", "GOP", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "VB", "NNP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 14, "answer": "I'm an idealist, and a romantic and a permanent optimist.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "an", "idealist", ",", "and", "a", "romantic", "and", "a", "permanent", "optimist", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["GOP"], "PERSON": ["Newt Gingrich"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mr. Cain"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", ",", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "RP", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 35, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 36, "answer": "She's come out in public because her name was revealed by the media, and she's decided, since her name is in the media now, that she wants to get the details of her complaint out since Mr. Cain is still denying any sexual harassment or impropriety.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "'s", "come", "out", "in", "public", "because", "her", "name", "was", "revealed", "by", "the", "media", ",", "and", "she", "'s", "decided", ",", "since", "her", "name", "is", "in", "the", "media", "now", ",", "that", "she", "wants", "to", "get", "the", "details", "of", "her", "complaint", "out", "since", "Mr.", "Cain", "is", "still", "denying", "any", "sexual", "harassment", "or", "impropriety", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 39, "question": "Is that the full extent of the alleged harassment?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "full", "extent", "of", "the", "alleged", "harassment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 40, "answer": "It certainly is not.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "certainly", "is", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 46, "question": "I suppose the obvious question -- and I put this to Sharon Bialek last night, another accuser -- is that given the passage of time, being, you know, over a decade, how is anyone going to prove anything?", "question_tokens": ["I", "suppose", "the", "obvious", "question", "--", "and", "I", "put", "this", "to", "Sharon", "Bialek", "last", "night", ",", "another", "accuser", "--", "is", "that", "given", "the", "passage", "of", "time", ",", "being", ",", "you", "know", ",", "over", "a", "decade", ",", "how", "is", "anyone", "going", "to", "prove", "anything", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ":", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "NN", ":", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBG", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBZ", "NN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 47, "answer": "It's not a question of proof.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "not", "a", "question", "of", "proof", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon Bialek"], "TIME": ["last night"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["1999"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "RB", "IN", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 56, "question": "Why is that?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 57, "answer": "My client settled this matter confidentially in 1999.", "answer_tokens": ["My", "client", "settled", "this", "matter", "confidentially", "in", "1999", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "EX", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 61, "question": "Can you confirm that your client was paid $45,000 to settle her complaint at the time?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "you", "confirm", "that", "your", "client", "was", "paid", "$", "45,000", "to", "settle", "her", "complaint", "at", "the", "time", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "$", "CD", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 62, "answer": "The amount of the settlement is confidential and I'm not going to get into the details of it but there was a monetary settlement.", "answer_tokens": ["The", "amount", "of", "the", "settlement", "is", "confidential", "and", "I", "'m", "not", "going", "to", "get", "into", "the", "details", "of", "it", "but", "there", "was", "a", "monetary", "settlement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"MONEY": ["$45,000"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Joel Bennett"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBD", ",", "WP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 65, "question": "What was the conversation that you had like?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "conversation", "that", "you", "had", "like", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 66, "answer": "Well, I think this is a woman, as Joel Bennett has said, who really didn't want to make this public.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "woman", ",", "as", "Joel", "Bennett", "has", "said", ",", "who", "really", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "make", "this", "public", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", ",", "RB", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "VB", "NNS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 80, "question": "Does this all ring true and familiar to you?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "this", "all", "ring", "true", "and", "familiar", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "DT", "VBG", "JJ", "CC", "JJ", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 81, "answer": "Well, you know, I was hoping that, you know, that Sharon, my client who has been very, very brave and very courageous, you know, would inspire others to speak out if they felt comfortable in doing so.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "I", "was", "hoping", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "that", "Sharon", ",", "my", "client", "who", "has", "been", "very", ",", "very", "brave", "and", "very", "courageous", ",", "you", "know", ",", "would", "inspire", "others", "to", "speak", "out", "if", "they", "felt", "comfortable", "in", "doing", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", ",", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", "IN", "NN", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 95, "question": "I mean what did you make of that when you saw him say that?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", "what", "did", "you", "make", "of", "that", "when", "you", "saw", "him", "say", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 96, "answer": "Well, you know, he seemed to shift from he couldn't recall, he doesn't know, and then it just -- you know, kind of dancing all over the place.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "know", ",", "he", "seemed", "to", "shift", "from", "he", "could", "n't", "recall", ",", "he", "does", "n't", "know", ",", "and", "then", "it", "just", "--", "you", "know", ",", "kind", "of", "dancing", "all", "over", "the", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Clarence Thomas", "Allred"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "VBG", "IN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "TO", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Do you think it's that serious?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "that", "serious", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "I don't -- as a presidential candidate, I don't know that there's any forum for doing that, unlike the Clarence Thomas confirmation hearings, but I would like to say that I was happy to say I hear Miss Allred say that she and her client would cooperate in a joint press conference, and I look forward to working with her on that.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "--", "as", "a", "presidential", "candidate", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "know", "that", "there", "'s", "any", "forum", "for", "doing", "that", ",", "unlike", "the", "Clarence", "Thomas", "confirmation", "hearings", ",", "but", "I", "would", "like", "to", "say", "that", "I", "was", "happy", "to", "say", "I", "hear", "Miss", "Allred", "say", "that", "she", "and", "her", "client", "would", "cooperate", "in", "a", "joint", "press", "conference", ",", "and", "I", "look", "forward", "to", "working", "with", "her", "on", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["14 years ago"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Reuters", "GOP"], "PERSON": ["Sharon Bialek", "Herman Cain", "Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "MD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "CD", "NNS", "RB", ",", "CC", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NNP", "VBZ", "NN", "IN", "IN", ":", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WDT", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNS", "VBZ", "VBG", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 114, "question": "Can Herman Cain survive?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "Herman", "Cain", "survive", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 115, "answer": "Well, I certainly can't speak to the credibility of his accusers and you know what happened 14 years ago, but we can look at the poll and Reuters has poll out after -- after Sharon Bialek's press conference yesterday that finds that Herman Cain's favorability among GOP voters is falling, and he's now behind Mitt Romney.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "certainly", "ca", "n't", "speak", "to", "the", "credibility", "of", "his", "accusers", "and", "you", "know", "what", "happened", "14", "years", "ago", ",", "but", "we", "can", "look", "at", "the", "poll", "and", "Reuters", "has", "poll", "out", "after", "--", "after", "Sharon", "Bialek", "'s", "press", "conference", "yesterday", "that", "finds", "that", "Herman", "Cain", "'s", "favorability", "among", "GOP", "voters", "is", "falling", ",", "and", "he", "'s", "now", "behind", "Mitt", "Romney", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 125, "question": "He looks in big trouble, doesn't he?", "question_tokens": ["He", "looks", "in", "big", "trouble", ",", "does", "n't", "he", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 126, "answer": "Yes, he is in big trouble.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "he", "is", "in", "big", "trouble", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 141, "question": "Could this open up doors for these other candidates?", "question_tokens": ["Could", "this", "open", "up", "doors", "for", "these", "other", "candidates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "DT", "JJ", "RP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 142, "answer": "You know, it's interesting.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "it", "'s", "interesting", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 150, "question": "Joel, I mean, would you bring your client on with other women who made accusations, maybe Sharon Bialek or others if they come forward on to this show and discuss this live?", "question_tokens": ["Joel", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "would", "you", "bring", "your", "client", "on", "with", "other", "women", "who", "made", "accusations", ",", "maybe", "Sharon", "Bialek", "or", "others", "if", "they", "come", "forward", "on", "to", "this", "show", "and", "discuss", "this", "live", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", "WP", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "RB", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "DT", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 151, "answer": "Well, the first step will be the joint press conference.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "the", "first", "step", "will", "be", "the", "joint", "press", "conference", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Sharon Bialek"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 189, "question": "Are you aware of this?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "aware", "of", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 190, "answer": "I was not aware of it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "not", "aware", "of", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 200, "question": "What do you put that down to?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "put", "that", "down", "to", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "."], "aSentId": 201, "answer": "Well, first of all, I tell people that the tortoise is the motto of our campaign.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "tell", "people", "that", "the", "tortoise", "is", "the", "motto", "of", "our", "campaign", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 230, "question": "What is it about you that to date hasn't really electrified the Republicans?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "it", "about", "you", "that", "to", "date", "has", "n't", "really", "electrified", "the", "Republicans", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "TO", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NNPS", "."], "aSentId": 231, "answer": "Well, I think there are two things.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "there", "are", "two", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "RB", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ":", "IN", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 244, "question": "Do you regret that in hindsight?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "that", "in", "hindsight", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 245, "answer": "Well, that's exactly -- it was the perfect thing to do -- for two reasons.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "exactly", "--", "it", "was", "the", "perfect", "thing", "to", "do", "--", "for", "two", "reasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "NNS", "WP", "VBD", "VBG", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 254, "question": "Why?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "."], "aSentId": 255, "answer": "Because we talked to people who were explaining the Greek view of the world.", "answer_tokens": ["Because", "we", "talked", "to", "people", "who", "were", "explaining", "the", "Greek", "view", "of", "the", "world", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "NNS", "WP", "RB", "VBP", "NN", "RP", "TO", "VB", "NN", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 261, "question": "To pre-guess the Greek economic crisis?", "question_tokens": ["To", "pre-guess", "the", "Greek", "economic", "crisis", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "JJ", "DT", "NNP", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 262, "answer": "No, what I'm going to tell you is having leaders who actually take time off to go learn something is a good thing.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "what", "I", "'m", "going", "to", "tell", "you", "is", "having", "leaders", "who", "actually", "take", "time", "off", "to", "go", "learn", "something", "is", "a", "good", "thing", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Herman Cain"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", ":", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 301, "question": "Is it unfair, though, to judge a man by his character?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "it", "unfair", ",", "though", ",", "to", "judge", "a", "man", "by", "his", "character", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "JJ", ",", "IN", ",", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 302, "answer": "Let me give you -- let me give you an example totally different than Herman Cain.", "answer_tokens": ["Let", "me", "give", "you", "--", "let", "me", "give", "you", "an", "example", "totally", "different", "than", "Herman", "Cain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "It is a little bit, isn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "is", "a", "little", "bit", ",", "is", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "It's a fact.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "fact", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "WP", "VBZ", "RP", "CC", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "WP", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "NNS", "VBZ", "NNS", "PRP", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 316, "question": "Do you think that's a vote getter whacking the media?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "that", "'s", "a", "vote", "getter", "whacking", "the", "media", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "VBG", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 317, "answer": "I think that - I think it's important if somebody who stands up and say s a great deal of what the American news media does makes it harder for us to govern ourselves and harder for us to solve our problems.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "-", "I", "think", "it", "'s", "important", "if", "somebody", "who", "stands", "up", "and", "say", "s", "a", "great", "deal", "of", "what", "the", "American", "news", "media", "does", "makes", "it", "harder", "for", "us", "to", "govern", "ourselves", "and", "harder", "for", "us", "to", "solve", "our", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 342, "question": "-- is that you're probably going to be, whether you like it or not, perceived as the anti-Mitt candidate, aren't you?", "question_tokens": ["--", "is", "that", "you", "'re", "probably", "going", "to", "be", ",", "whether", "you", "like", "it", "or", "not", ",", "perceived", "as", "the", "anti-Mitt", "candidate", ",", "are", "n't", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": [":", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "PRP", "CC", "RB", ",", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 343, "answer": "This is something I find fascinating.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "something", "I", "find", "fascinating", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "TO", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 364, "question": "So you won't be doing that?", "question_tokens": ["So", "you", "wo", "n't", "be", "doing", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 365, "answer": "First of all, I think I am a differential to the other candidates.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "I", "am", "a", "differential", "to", "the", "other", "candidates", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 366, "question": "How do you differ to Mitt Romney?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "differ", "to", "Mitt", "Romney", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 367, "answer": "I just said it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "just", "said", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "JJ", "JJR", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 381, "question": "Is he a conservative in the true sense?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "he", "a", "conservative", "in", "the", "true", "sense", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 382, "answer": "He is certainly much more conservative than Barack Obama.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "is", "certainly", "much", "more", "conservative", "than", "Barack", "Obama", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNPS", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 397, "question": "Can the traditional hard line conservative values still be successful, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["Can", "the", "traditional", "hard", "line", "conservative", "values", "still", "be", "successful", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "JJ", "NNS", "RB", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 398, "answer": "Well, a majority of Americans now believe in the right to life.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "a", "majority", "of", "Americans", "now", "believe", "in", "the", "right", "to", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "CC", "NN", "CC", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 402, "question": "Are you anti-abortion under any circumstances?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "anti-abortion", "under", "any", "circumstances", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 403, "answer": "I think that there are exceptions for life of the mother and rape and incest.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "there", "are", "exceptions", "for", "life", "of", "the", "mother", "and", "rape", "and", "incest", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", ",", "JJS", "JJ", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 434, "question": "And also, where do you think you differ, if you do, from the Tea Party and their aspirations in that area?", "question_tokens": ["And", "also", ",", "where", "do", "you", "think", "you", "differ", ",", "if", "you", "do", ",", "from", "the", "Tea", "Party", "and", "their", "aspirations", "in", "that", "area", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 435, "answer": "Well, first of all, I think with Obama, he's the best, most effective Food Stamp president in history.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "with", "Obama", ",", "he", "'s", "the", "best", ",", "most", "effective", "Food", "Stamp", "president", "in", "history", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Tea Party"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "TO", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 449, "question": "Do you regret that?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "regret", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 450, "answer": "No, it was the right thing to do.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "was", "the", "right", "thing", "to", "do", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 451, "question": "It ultimately led to you losing your job, didn't it?", "question_tokens": ["It", "ultimately", "led", "to", "you", "losing", "your", "job", ",", "did", "n't", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "PRP", "VBG", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "VBD", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 452, "answer": "No, it had nothing to do with me losing my job.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "it", "had", "nothing", "to", "do", "with", "me", "losing", "my", "job", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 461, "question": "Do you think you don't get the credit you deserve?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "think", "you", "do", "n't", "get", "the", "credit", "you", "deserve", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 462, "answer": "I don't worry about it.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "worry", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "JJ", "NN", ",", "NN", "JJ", ",", "JJ", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 481, "question": "What would be your simple remedy to get America back to work?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "your", "simple", "remedy", "to", "get", "America", "back", "to", "work", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "RB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 482, "answer": "Repeal the Dodd/Frank bill immediately, repeal Sarbanes/Oxley, repeal Obama-care, eliminate the capital gains tax.", "answer_tokens": ["Repeal", "the", "Dodd/Frank", "bill", "immediately", ",", "repeal", "Sarbanes/Oxley", ",", "repeal", "Obama-care", ",", "eliminate", "the", "capital", "gains", "tax", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RP", "IN", "JJ", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 500, "question": "I mean, what has happened to America?", "question_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "what", "has", "happened", "to", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "VBN", "TO", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 501, "answer": "I think that we got off on several wrong tracks.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "we", "got", "off", "on", "several", "wrong", "tracks", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", "."], "qSentId": 508, "question": "Are you an incurable romantic?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "you", "an", "incurable", "romantic", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 509, "answer": "Yes.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "VB", "PRP", "VB", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 517, "question": "What would be the first things you would do to restore American pride?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "the", "first", "things", "you", "would", "do", "to", "restore", "American", "pride", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 518, "answer": "Well, let me say, first of all, I think that the recovery will begin late on election night.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "let", "me", "say", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "I", "think", "that", "the", "recovery", "will", "begin", "late", "on", "election", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBP", "CD", "NNS", "TO", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 527, "question": "What would you do about it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "about", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 528, "answer": "I think there are two answers to why we have fallen behind.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "are", "two", "answers", "to", "why", "we", "have", "fallen", "behind", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "RB", "CC", "WRB", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "VBN", "RB", "RBR", "IN", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "RP", "CC", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "CC", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 542, "question": "And what have you learned about yourself from things that haven't gone the right way?", "question_tokens": ["And", "what", "have", "you", "learned", "about", "yourself", "from", "things", "that", "have", "n't", "gone", "the", "right", "way", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 543, "answer": "I think there were times in my life when I was too lonely and when I would have been much better off to have sat down with very close friends and opened up and talked through that phase of my life and tried to do things.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "there", "were", "times", "in", "my", "life", "when", "I", "was", "too", "lonely", "and", "when", "I", "would", "have", "been", "much", "better", "off", "to", "have", "sat", "down", "with", "very", "close", "friends", "and", "opened", "up", "and", "talked", "through", "that", "phase", "of", "my", "life", "and", "tried", "to", "do", "things", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 554, "question": "I'm not -- by the way, I'm not assuming this is going you have to do for a while?", "question_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "--", "by", "the", "way", ",", "I", "'m", "not", "assuming", "this", "is", "going", "you", "have", "to", "do", "for", "a", "while", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VBG", "DT", "VBZ", "VBG", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 555, "answer": "No, no, no I'm thinking.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "I", "'m", "thinking", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Africa"]}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "CD", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "NNS", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBG", "TO", "NNP", "CC", "VBG", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 557, "question": "What instinctively comes to mind as the great moment of your life?", "question_tokens": ["What", "instinctively", "comes", "to", "mind", "as", "the", "great", "moment", "of", "your", "life", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "RB", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 558, "answer": "I think probably one of my greatest moments of my life was going to Africa and seeing animals.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "probably", "one", "of", "my", "greatest", "moments", "of", "my", "life", "was", "going", "to", "Africa", "and", "seeing", "animals", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNS", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", ":", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "RP", "IN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 560, "question": "Would you really?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 561, "answer": "Yes, I mean, I -- when you say to me about really great moments of happiness, it is hanging out at zoos.", "answer_tokens": ["Yes", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "I", "--", "when", "you", "say", "to", "me", "about", "really", "great", "moments", "of", "happiness", ",", "it", "is", "hanging", "out", "at", "zoos", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 566, "question": "What was the animal spot or whatever it was?", "question_tokens": ["What", "was", "the", "animal", "spot", "or", "whatever", "it", "was", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "RB", "PRP", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 567, "answer": "Oh, I think it was probably being on the Serengeti Plain.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "I", "think", "it", "was", "probably", "being", "on", "the", "Serengeti", "Plain", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "111108pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", ",", "DT", ",", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 574, "question": "A year from now, you seeing -- you extend the metaphor, you seeing antelope, Barack Obama, cheetah, Newt Gingrich?", "question_tokens": ["A", "year", "from", "now", ",", "you", "seeing", "--", "you", "extend", "the", "metaphor", ",", "you", "seeing", "antelope", ",", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "cheetah", ",", "Newt", "Gingrich", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "IN", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBG", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBG", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "NN", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 575, "answer": "No, no, no.", "answer_tokens": ["No", ",", "no", ",", "no", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama", "Newt Gingrich"]}}]